Good morning.
おはよう
Hey, for today...
ね　今日の準備ってさ
Yeah?
We need an afro, joke glasses... and what else?
まずアフロと　鼻眼鏡の配達
Were you up late last night?
昨日夜更かしでもしたんですか
うちのクラスの文化祭費用
Yeah, I couldn't figure out how to allocate
割り振りが決んなくて
the cultural festival budget for our class.
それをずっと考えてたら
I was up all night thinking it over.
生徒会と学級委員を掛け持ちしてると忙しいですね
You must be busy as both a class rep and a member of the student council.
文化祭近いと余計な
It's even worse with the festival coming u—
Shun-chan, Kanamecchi!
春ちゃん　要っち
Good mammaring!
おっぱい
（注：おっぱい和おはよう的头字都是お所以有些色鬼爱用おっぱい说早安）
So Shun, what's your class doing?
で　春のクラスは何やんだ
Oh, my class is...
あのう　うちのクラスは
H-Hey, don't ignore me!
ちょっちょっと　無視しないでよ
朝のあいさつは基本でしょう
You're supposed to say hello!
They responded to that correctly.
今のが春たちの方が正しい反応だよね
Yup.
だよね
I don't believe you two!
なんだよ　ゆっきーたちまで
あの　千鶴君
Um, Chizuru-kun...
Ignore him. There's no point in even replying.
ほっとっけよ
フォローするだけ無駄だから
で　春のクラスはなにすんだ
So Shun, what's your class doing?
We're doing a café with a twist.
僕らはちょっと変わった喫茶店をやるんです
Yeah, everyone's gonna cross-dress.
そう　店員は衣装男女逆に着るんだよね
男女逆
Cross-dress?
Really? Awesome!
まじ　すげえ
要君たちのクラスは何をするんですか
Kaname-kun, what's your class doing?
ベタにお化け屋敷
A stereotypical haunted house.
yappari kimi da yo ne
Oh hey, it's you?
honto odoroita yo
You startled me
futari yoku aruita namikidoori
Here we are, on the tree-lined road we walked so often
otona ni naru no wo
I couldn't wait to grow up, and kept you at a distance, didn't I?
matezu ni toozaketeitta no wa watashi datta ne
itsumo
As always,
mainasu ichido no ame ga furu
the icy rain falls
kimi ga kureta namida
comprised of tears you cried for me
sono yasashisa made wakaranakute
That kindness I didn't understand
zutto kono mune wo shimetsuketa
lay heavy on my heart all the time
mainasu ichido no ame ga furu
The icy rain falls
tsumetasugiru namida
comprised of tears unbearably cold
hagurakasu taido ni okotteta keredo
Although I was angry at my evasive personality
本字幕由诸神字幕组(kamigami.org)制作,仅供学习交流之用
若您喜欢本作品,请支持正版影像制品
---诸神字幕组---
日听 バサラ     翻译 景寒筱    日校 慧慧 喵儿
总校 有明の月     时间轴 葛蔓     压制 PHENOTYPE
jitsu wa sukuwareteita n da ne
you cured me of that, didn't you
There isn't much time 'til the festival.
文化祭まで時間もないので
Use this extended homeroom period effectively and work on your projects.
このロングホームルームを有効に使って
各自作業を進めてください
以上です
That is all.
With the cultural festival approaching, the classroom
文化祭が近づき
教室の中はどこか隠せない期待と
is overflowing with irrepressible anticipation...
心地よい騒がしさと
comforting bustle...
トラブルにあふれている
and trouble.
ねね　塚原君
Hey, Tsukahara-kun.
What do you think of advertising by walking around the school
当日宣伝も兼ねてお化けの衣装を着ながら
in our haunted house costumes with placards?
看板持って校内回るのとかどう
Doesn't that sound interesting?
面白くない？
What?
はぁ？予算ぎりぎりだし　いいよ　やんないで
We're already pushing the budget.
We don't need to do that.
ポスター作るし
We're making posters.
What? But the flashier it is, the more people we'll attract!
でも　派手にやった方が絶対受けるし
That's right.
Well, Tsukahara-kun?
どう　塚原君
Well, I'll see if we can shift some money from somewhere else.
じゃ　他で経費削れるとこないか
検討してみっから
やった
Great!
Thanks!
よろしくね
ね　どんなのにする
What should we do?
What about a kappa?
That sounds good, doesn't it?
カッパとかどうかな
かっこよくないカッパ
Budget Recalculation
Hey, Tsukahara.
なあなあ　塚原
How do I go about getting blackout curtains from the school?
暗幕ってどうやって学校側から借りればいいんだっけ
What? You haven't gotten any yet?
はぁ　まだ借りてねえのかよ
早くしねえと他のクラスに取られんぞ
If you don't hurry,
someone else will get to them before us!
Sorry, sorry.
悪い悪い　でどうやんの
So, how do I get them?
まず生徒会室に行って
Go to the Student Council Office,
get an equipment request form and fill out...
備品貸出書をもらって
それに使用目的とか
めんどくせぇ
That's too much work.
It's more work for me to keep on explaining it to you!
何度も説明する俺の方がめんどくせよ
Tsukahara-kun, do you have a minute?
塚原君　ちょっといい
当日の係なんだけど
It's about assigning roles on the day of the festival.
Could you look at this?
これ見て
Oh, this is...
あ　それは
Hold on, Tsukahara.
What about the curtains?
ちょっとちょっと　塚原
暗幕は
Tsu-ka-ha-ra!
塚原
Fine! I'll do it!
いい　俺がやっとく
Really?
Budget Recalculation
えっ　まじで
Blackout
いやーんさっすが塚原君　やあー
Man, you're the greatest!
Shut up.
うっせ
Damn, it's always this, that or the other.
くっそうなんでこう次から次へと
じゃ　誰がなんの係をするかは
I guess we'll decide roles later.
後で決めるってことで
あ　よろしく
Yeah, thanks.
Hey, Yuuki and that monkey—I mean, Tachibana... where'd they go?
な　祐希と子ザル　あ　いや　橘　どこ行った
Yuu-ta.
悠太　春ちゃん
Shun-chan.
What are you doing? Don't you have homeroom, too?
どうしたの
そっちもホームルーム中でしょう
あのね　二人に見せたいものがあってね
There's something I want to show you two.
Ta-da!
ジャジャーン　俺とゆっきーの力作
Yukki and I made them!
Our environmentally-friendly eco-trains!
地球にやさしいエコトレイン
Half of the train is made out of kindness.
この電車の半分はやさしさでできています
Are you using that in your haunted house?
ああー　それお化け屋敷で使うんですか
What? No.
え？　使わないよ
使わないのに作ったんですね
They made it even though they won't use it...
準備で忙しいこの時期に
Even though everyone's busy with preparations...
悠太　乗って乗って
Get in, Yuuta. I'll pull you.
引っ張ってあげる
うーん　でも今　準備中だし
But we're in the middle of preparations.
All right then, your big brother will ride it.
じゃ　お兄ちゃん乗っちゃおうかな
ねえ　祐希君
Okay, Yuuki-kun?
Mandarins
How is it, sir?
どうですか　お客さん
まさに箱入り息子
You look safe and snug in that box!
そうですか　箱詰めされてるって感じですけど
Really?
But it feels more like I'm trapped in a box...
お客さん　どこ行きます
Where would you like to go, sir?
どこへでも行きますよ
We can go anywhere.
決められたレールの上を走らないのがモットーですから
Straying off the beaten path is our motto.
Whose lazy son are you?
どこのドラ息子ですか
あー　じゃ　東先生のところまでお願いします
Please take us to Azuma-sensei.
There's something I want to borrow from him.
ちょうど　お借りしたい資料があるので
ラジャーっす
Roger.
The eco-train is departing.
では　エコトレイン出発しまー
That's not fair!
卑怯だぞ　それ
くっそー　底抜け機能を搭載していたとは
Damn it!
I can't believe you installed a bottomless feature!
I was caught off guard!
迂闊なり
Since when did cardboard boxes become so high-tech?
段ボールってそんな高性能でしたっけ
Sir, please entrust me with your life!
お客さん　その命　私に預けてください
What?
Speed up!
スピードアップ
あ あのう
U-Um...
Curve!
はい　カーブ
And we've arrived.
ひとまず到着
Uh, um... Chizuru-kun...
あのあの　千鶴君
What's with th—
どうしたの　その
The sweat? Don't worry about it.
汗ですか　気にしないでください
Not the sweat.
汗じゃなくて　それ
What's that?
Please don't worry about it.
あまり気にしないでください
それより東先生に用が
More importantly, I had something to ask...
What was it?
あれ　何だっけ
Azuma-sensei.
東先生　あの　資料をお借りしたいんですけど
Um, I want to borrow some materials...
Another one? Is this a new fad?
また　それ　流行ってるの？
へへへ　どうでしょう
I'm not sure.
このずるゆっきー
Yukki, you cheater!
I won't lose next time!
次は負けねえからな
I've installed my own bottomless feature!
うちも底抜け機能搭載したからな
That's just broken, isn't it?
壊れただけでしょう　それ
Will this do?
はい　これでいいかな
Alice in Wonderland
Yes, thank you.
はい　ありがとうございます
皆文化祭の準備はどう　順調
How are your preparations for the festival coming along?
I trust it's going well?
Yes.
はい
People from outside the school will be coming for the festival,
文化祭は一般の方も遊びに来るから　がんばらないとね
so do your best.
Azuma-sensei, bring your girlfriend to the festival!
東先生
文化祭に彼女連れてきてくださいよ
What?
あ　でも　寂しいことに今　彼女いないから
Unfortunately... I don't have a girlfriend at the moment.
What a surprise.
意外です
東先生もてそうなのに
I figured you'd be popular.
やさしいし　格好いいし
You're so kind and handsome, after all.
まさか　一人に収まる気はないとか
Maybe he doesn't want to settle on just one!
He goes through girls like pages of a daily calendar.
女は日めくりカレンダーなんですね
That's not it.
違うから
あー　なんていうか
Well, you know how girls act all cutesy and energetic?
あのキャピキャピってしたノリが苦手というか
I've never been able to deal with it very well.
あのノリで来られるのが昔からダメで
Really?
あぁ　そうなんですか
昔からもてたんだな
He's always been popular...
そういえば　塚原君は
So, where's Tsukahara-kun?
要っちは
Kanamecchi is...
俺がどうしたって
What about me?
Huh?
祐希　子ザル
Yuuki, Monkey...
何やってんだよ　あぁ！？
What are you doing, huh?
Kanamecchi!
要っち
Huh? W-Wait— Yukki!
ちょ　ちょっと　ゆっきー
時間がねえって分かってんのか
Don't you realize we don't have time for this?
お前ら
Ow!
あいたー
Why just me?
何で俺だけ
Jeez. The extended homeroom period ended and you guys have done nothing.
ったく
お前らが何もしない間に
ロングホームルームが終わったじゃねえか
Shun and Yuuta, head back to your classroom.
ほら　春たちも教室に帰れ
You left the class rep in the lurch.
学級委員が困ってるぞ
Oh, right. We were in the middle of making flowers.
そうですね
花作りも途中だったし
You two, as well.
ほら　お前らも
Yeah, yeah.
はーい
大変そうだね
They're hard work, aren't they?
It's nothing new.
別に いつものことですから
あまり無理しないでね
Don't push yourself too hard.
別に無理なんか
I'm not...
You And I
Matsuoka-kun, Asaba-kun!
松岡君　浅羽君
当日の衣装　どれがいい
Which costume do you want to wear at the festival?
ああー　かわいいですね
They're all so cute. I don't know which to choose.
迷います
You can't choose?
迷うんだ
What?
I'm sure you two would look good in anything!
でも二人ならどんな衣装も似合いそうだよね
Yeah!
Really?
そうですか
Cheshire!
I bet they'd look good in these, too!
皆も似合いそうですよね
はい
What?
ゆっきー　これが俺たちの初体験になるんだね
Yukki.
This will be our first time...
初体験に
Our first time...
Chizuru-san...
千鶴さん　君ね　中学生じゃないんだから
You know, you're not in middle school any more.
Stop getting giddy every time someone says it's their first time.
初体験って言葉にいちいち燥がないの
You're just using the copier for the first time.
初めでコピー機使うだけでしょう
めんごめんご　ゆっきーはコピー機使ったことあんの
Sowwie, sowwie.
Yukki, have you used a copier before?
It's my first time, too.
いや　俺も初めて
ゆっきーも初体験だ
Yukki, it's your first time, too!
Your first... first time...
Starting copying.
コピー開始します
初体験
Start
Stop
Divide
Reset
Huh? It's blank?!
ええ　真っ白
I think it's trying to throw us off by not spitting out copies easily.
簡単にはコピらせないとゆさぶりをかけてきてるのかもね
悪い　ちょっと先に使っていいか
Sorry, can I skip ahead of you?
I'm in a hurry.
急いでたから
Go ahead.
どうぞ
Ah, so that's how you do it...
2—4 Cultural Festival
•List of different work groups
Costume making group
Meeting hall prep group
Receiving group
Ghost volunteer group
Prop creating group
Tour guide group
•Types of creatures
Sadako
Toilet ghost Hanako
Lantern demon
Jason
Zombies
Ghosts
Other major monsters
Jiang Shi vampire
•Necessary equipment
Blackout curtains
そういうテクがあったとは
Place the original face down!
コピりたい面は下
I'll be copying that technique!
この技パクらせてもらうぜ
Don't you feel like we're getting better at making copies...
パクるとか
その時点で　今の俺たちちょっとコピー上手って感じ
because we're copying others?
そうともよ
Spot on.
As experts at copying, we'll get it right this time—
俺たちコピー上手は次こそ完璧に
ええ？　何これ
Huh?
2—4 Cultural
•List of different work groups
Costume making group
Meeting hall prep group
Receiving group
•Types of creatures
Sadako
Toilet ghost Hanako
Lantern demon
Gho
Pro
Tou
Zombies
Ghosts
Other m
What is this?
何　どんどん出てきてるじゃん
Hey look, they keep coming!
ごめん　要が8枚って言ったから　8のボタン押しちゃった
Sorry.
Kaname asked for eight sheets, so I pressed eight.
What?!
どうやって止めんのよ　こいつ
How do we stop this thing?
おい　ストップ　ストップ
Hey, stop! Stop!
Good...
よかった
よくないよ　ほら
It's not good. Look.
失敗コピーが無駄に8枚
We made eight wasteful, failed copies.
How terrible for the planet.
なんて地球に厳しい
もう　何これ
What's wrong with this thing?
Technology is meant to be making our lives easier!
便利な世の中になったんとちゃうんかい
Oh, I know the reason. It must be because technology advances so quickly that humans can't keep up.
きっとあれだよ
科学の発達がすごすぎて
逆に人間の手に負えなくなりつつあるんだよ
この調子だとロボットが人間に牙を剥く日も近いんじゃないかな
It won't be long before robots turn against humans.
That actually might be possible.
あり得るね　それ
バカじゃねえの　お前ら
What are you, stupid?
あ　要
Kaname.
I only asked for eight copies.
たかが　コピー8枚頼んだだけなのに
Why are you wasting so much time on this?
いつまで手こずってってんだよ
Wow, Kanamecchi! You're brilliant!
すっげえ　要っち
天才
お前らも天才だけどな　あほの
And you're brilliant... at being stupid.
あ　浅羽君たち居た
There you are!
今ね　教室で当日どの係をやりたいか
We're asking people what role they want to have during the festival.
希望出してもらってるんだけど
うぃー　今行きまーす
We'll be right there!
Tsukahara-senpai! Good timing!
塚原先輩　いいところに
Senpai! Three classes want to use the home economics classroom on the day of the festival.
先輩　当日家庭科室を使いたいクラスが三つかぶっちゃって
Their reps are arguing about it in the Student Council Office right now.
今代表者たちが生徒会室でもめてるんですよ
What?
Senpai, do something!
先輩何とかしてください
Do something?
なんとかって
要　行かないの
Kaname, aren't you coming?
Huh? Um...
え？　えーっとあの
Senpai, hurry up!
先輩　早く
えーはいはい　今行くっつーの
Okay, I'm coming.
Yuuki, you know that name-thing...
祐希　お前あれだ
名前付け　じゃない　名前んとこ　あ
I mean, the place where you...
Huh?
受付　受付んとこ
Huh? What?
Reception! The reception desk!
ええ　なに
Put my name down for that!
俺の名前出しとけ
ええ　受付
Reception? Boring.
つまんない
More like, he's stumbling over his words...
っていうか　噛みすぎ
Hey, Princess.
そこのお嬢さん
What are you doing?
何やってんの
当日着る衣装の裾合わせをしてるんですよ
We're getting fitted for our outfits for the festival.
今は仮縫いの順番待ち
We're waiting to be tacked.
Yuuki! Monkey! Where are you?
祐希　子ザル　どこだ
Uh-oh, it's Kanamecchi!
やば　要っちだ
Didn't take him long to notice.
気付くの早かったね
Did you do something to make him mad again?
君たち　また何か怒らせるようなことを
Um...
Can you hide us for a bit?
ちょっと匿まってください
What?
はい
くそ　どこ行きやがった
Damn it, where'd they go?
Shun, Yuuta, have you seen Yuuki and the monkey?
春　悠太
祐希と子ザル見なかったか
Nope.
いえ　全然
N-N-No, is something wrong?
全然　どどどかしたんですか
I said I wanted to work at reception during the festival,
文化祭当日の係
俺は受付をやるっつったのに
but I'm signed up to be a ghost.
お化け役になってんだよ
ぜってーあいつらが勝手に
I know they did it.
っつか　お前ら愉快な格好してんな
Hey, you guys look rather fetching.
What are those? Your outfits for...
何これ
もしかして当日の
ごめんなさい
Sorry!
Hey.
おい
お前スカートの中見せろ
Let me look under your skirt.
What?
Just flip it up already!
いいから　めくれってんだよ
D-Don't do...
ちょちょちょっと　やめ
Just let me see!
いいから　見せろ
Hey, you can't!
ちょっと困ります
Why not?
なんでだ
Oh my, Kaname-san, what a bold pervert you are.
要さん　あなた
痴漢のわりに大胆
What? That's not what I'm doing!
ちげえよ　バカ
っつか　こいつのスカートの中見たって
You think I'd enjoy looking up his skirt?
全然楽しくねえだろうが
何言ってんの
What do you mean?
この中には要の知らない未知の世界が広がってるかも
There might be a strange world unknown to you under there.
What are trying to say?!
お前何言ってんだ　あほか
Are you stupid?
Nice one, Yuutan!
悠太　Nice
Keep distracting him!
そのまま話を逸らして
Hey, don't start imagining weird things!
もう　二人とも勝手な言い合いしないでください
I'm wearing a jersey under here!
僕この下ジャージ穿いてますから
Then...
だったら
尚更見せたって問題ねえだろが
You shouldn't have any problems with letting me take a look!
Just let me look!
いい加減に　みせろってんだよ
ダメです
No!
Enough already...
いい加減に観念しろ
Y-You pervert.
へ　変態
Um... this isn't...!
いや　こりゃ　違う
Awful! You're awful!
最低　あんた最低よ
How dare you! How dare you do that to Shun-chan!
春ちゃんに　春ちゃんに
You've got the wrong...
何勘違いして
Hey! You guys aren't getting away!
ってそこ
逃げられると思うなよ
最近要っちイライラしてるわよね
You've been awfully cranky lately.
Well, being cranky is practically a hobby for him.
まあ　この人はもともとイライラするのは趣味みたいなもんですけどね
Just whose fault do you think that is?
誰のせいだ　誰の
Kaname, can you make enlarged copies?
要　拡大コピーってできる
Huh? Why?
あー　なんで
The Manga Society asked me to do this huge favor and make enlarged copies of their advertisement posters,
漫研の宣伝ポスター用に拡大コピーしろって大技要求されて
困ってたんだよ
but I don't really want to.
要やってよ
You do it.
I can't believe you're asking me for favors after I got mad at you.
お前怒られた直後によく頼みごとできんな
Fine.
まあ　いいぜ
コピード下手のお前の頼みとありゃ
I suppose I'll have to help, considering how bad—
塚原　ちょっと来てくれよ
Tsukahara!
We need you for a moment.
Something terrible happened.
なんかやべえことんなっちゃってさ
Sure.
コピー後でいいか　ちょっと
Can your copies wait? I have to...
Huh? Sure.
塚原　こっちこっち　急いで
Tsukahara, this way. Hurry!
Okay.
—
Budget Recalculation
Blackout curtains
What is this? Blackout curtains?
なんだっけ　これ
暗幕
Blackout—
あんま…
Blackout curtains?
暗幕ですか
残ってないですよ　もう
There aren't any left.
N-None?
全然？
No.
はい
Not a single one?
一枚も
はい
N-No.
先輩？
S-Senpai?
Your class is putting on a haunted house?
先輩のクラスお化け屋敷やるんですか
That will need tons of curtains.
めちゃくちゃ暗幕使うじゃないですか
You should've turned in your request sooner...
もっと早く提出してもらわないと
先輩
Senpai?
You're right.
そうだよな　お化け屋敷だもんな
We're running a haunted house. Right.
そうだよなって
"I'm right?"
こうなると今から準備の簡単な出し物に変更するとか
You'll have to change it into something simple to prepare, or...
That won't be easy.
それもかなり無理があるよ
Yeah, but...
だ　だってさ
大丈夫だよ
It's okay.
A bunch of classes took extra just in case they needed them.
念のためとか言って取りすぎてるクラスが　たくさんあってね
You should have enough if you borrow some from them.
そこから分けてもらえば十分足りると思うよ
I see.
なるほど
You're right.
そうよね
Blackout curtains
15 sheets
Number of items :
Purpose:
To use in the haunted house
for the cultural festival
Note:
Teacher Seal of Approval
Your request has been approved.
じゃ　貸出OKということで
Here.
はい
Approved
Good luck with your haunted house.
お化け屋敷がんばってね
Approved
Thanks.
はい
We're almost done with props...
ええと　小道具はほとんどできて
All the roles have been decided...
当日の係も決まって
ね　暗幕は
Where are the curtains?
Tsukahara, what happened with the curtains?
塚原　暗幕って　どうなった
Huh? Yeah, I got some.
あ?　あー借りた借りた
Oh, thanks a lot, man!
まじでThank you
You shouldn't make others do your work for you!
ちょっと　あんたたち人に任せてないで
ちゃんと仕事しなさいよ
So what? Tsukahara's more reliable than me.
まあまあいいじゃん
だって俺らより塚原のが確実じゃん
You're useless!
あんたたちは使えなさ過ぎんの
ひでえ
You're so mean.
Budget Recalculation
Blackout curtains
Hey, hey, Shun-chan, I'm gonna be a ghost.
春ちゃん　春ちゃん
俺ね　お化け役やるんだけどね
What kind do you think I should be?
どれがいいと思う
うーん　そうですね
Let's see...
全身タイツなんてどうですか
How do you feel about a spandex bodysuit?
A spandex bodysuit?
全身タイツ
Yes.
はい
Why would I wear that?
なんでそうなるの
祐希　漫研って文化祭なんかやるの
Yuuki, is the Manga Society doing anything for the festival?
A manga café.
マンガ喫茶
Apparently, they do it every year.
なんか毎年それやってんだって
I see.
祐希　漫研のポスターのコピーまだだったよな
Yuuki, I haven't copied the posters for the Manga Society yet.
Can it wait until tomorrow?
明日とかでも
Huh? Forget about it.
あー　いいよ　あれもうやったから
I already did it.
というか　やってもらった
Well, Yuuta did it for me.
悠太君に
なんか悠太も拡大コピー分かるっていうしさ
Yuuta said he knew how to make enlarged copies, too.
I might as well have him do it if I'm asking you.
まあ要に頼むなら悠太　みたいな
んだよ　それ
What does that mean?
You're working so hard, I wasn't sure you could fit it in.
だって要ってさ
がんばりすぎで危険っていうか
上手く出来てもどっかマグレ臭いとこあるじゃん
I reckoned it'd only turn out well by sheer luck.
Yeah, you're so unreliable.
ね　なんか当てになんないよね
I know what you mean.
分かる分かる
Kanamecchi? Is something wrong?
要っち
どうった？
あー　そう！
I get it!
Ow! Why only me?
いってぇー　俺だけかよ
もう　文化祭前に喧嘩しないで下さいよ
Don't fight before the festival.
The days leading up to the festival were like a storm.
文化祭に続く
嵐のような毎日
If I lost focus for a minute, I'd be swept away.
一瞬でも気を抜けば流されてしまいそうで
Kaname-kun, don't be angry...
要君も怒らないでく
But if I got swept away, I'd see a change of scenery.
でも流されたら流されたで違う景色が見えてくる
ああー　　もう　怒った怒った
Now you've done it!
Just wait until you see what kind of ghost I'll make you be!
要っちはすっげえ変なお化け役にするもんね
Bring it on!
おお　やってみろよ
I'll use my Student Council influence to make you perform
当日お前が一人でひょっとこ踊りをするライブ
a Hyottoko dance all by yourself at the festival.
生徒会の力でパンフレットに組み込んでやっからよ
What? You can't do that!
ええ　そんな
要　それ完璧職権乱用だよね
Kaname, that's an obvious abuse of power...
Of course it is. Power's no good if you don't use it.
ったりめえだ　権力は使ってなんぼだ
Shun-chan, Kanamecchi's being mean!
春ちゃん　要っちが
Careful, Chizuru-kun!
危ないですよ　千鶴君
boku wa nakimushi de kuyashikute dakedo
It pains me to be such a crybaby,
anata ni ima tsutaetai n da
but I want to tell you my feelings right now
tada massugu ni boku wo mitsumeru tsuyokute
There you stand, silently gazing at me
Giving me the chance to answer the strength and tenderness in your eyes
yasashii sono hitomi ni kotaeru tame ni
itsushika miushinatteta ichiban taisetsu na mono mo
you taught me about what I lost sight of
sotto anata ga oshiete kureta
that was most important to me
tashika ni sou omoeru kara
I have no doubts about that
boku wa yowamushi de iya datta dakedo
I hated how weak I was
motto motto tsuyoku naru kara
but I will continue to become stronger
anata no koto wo mamoreru you na boku ni naru kara
I will be someone who could protect you
dakara sukoshi mattete
so wait a little longer for me
次回
Next time: On your mark.